http://www.jellenproducts.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
Shop By:
1-800-277-2250
Phone Orders (24 hrs)
SKIN CARE DEVICES
Blue LightElectrical FacialExfoliationFacial SteamerFacial ToningHair Growth LaserHigh FrequencyInfrared Light TherapyLED Light TherapyLow Level LaserMicrocurrentMicrodermabrasionMulti-FunctionPhotorejuvenatonRed Light TherapyUltrasonic Facial
SKIN CARE CONCERNS
AcneAge SpotsAging SkinBlackheadsBruisesCelluliteClogged PoresCold SoresCrow's FeetDark Eye CirclesDry SkinDull Skin ToneEczemaEye PuffinessFine LinesHair LossHyperpigmentationLarge PoresMelasmaOily SkinPain ReliefPoor Skin TextureRednessRosaceaSagging SkinScarsThinning HairUnwanted HairWound CareWrinkles
SKIN CARE PRODUCTS
CleansersConductive GelsCreamsExfoliatorsFoamsGelsLotionsPeelsScrubsSerumsToners
ACCESSORIES
AttachmentsCosmetic PackagingHigh Frequency ElectrodesPower Adapters & CordsProtective Appliance CoversProtective EyewearReplacement PartsTips and FiltersVoltage & Travel Converters
SALES
BRANDS
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience: Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website: We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer service: Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and selecting 'Your Account Details'.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms & Conditions.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 12/15/2013.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Jellen Products, Inc. 8374 Market Street, #101 Lakewood Ranch, Florida 34202 United States 1-800-277-2250
WHERE SKIN CARE MEETS TECHNOLOGY™
FREE SHIPPING OVER $99
Within The Continental U.S.
INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING
To Select Regions (See Details)
30-DAY MONEY BACK
Guarantee On Eligible Items
ORDER BY PHONE
1-800-277-2250 (24 Hrs)
CONNECT WITH US:
NEWSLETTER
Your Email Address:
POPULAR ARTICLES
Benefits of High Frequency Facial Treatment
Ultrasonic Facial Treatment For Aging Skin
What Do Microcurrent Facials Do For The Skin?
© 2005- Jellen Products, Inc. | Franklin, TN 37027 USA | Phone: 1-800-277-2250
